Guide to the Thain White Papers 1877-1983
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula,
- Photographs, 1877-1976; Series VIII; 2.75 linear feet; 758 photographs
  - Boats and Planes, 1905-1982; Subseries 2; 0.4 linear feet; 131 photos
    - Small group of people in an early speedboat of some kind, undated; 137(VIII):388
    - Three men near shore, 1 sitting in an unidentified small boat, undated; 137(VIII):389
    - Large crowd of people waiting to board an unidentified ship, undated; 137(VIII):390
    - Large crowd of people boarding The New Klondike, circa 1921; 137(VIII):391
    - Small boat near Glacier National Park, undated; 137(VIII):392
    - Steamboat Kalispell Rollins, Montana on Flathead Lake, undated; 72-356
    - Tugboats built for O'Brian Lumber Co., later Somer Lumber Co., Flathead Lake, circa 1904; 72-357
    - Steamboat Tom Carver on Flathead Lake, undated; 72-358
    - Steamboat City of Dixon on Flathead Lake, 1912; 72-359
    - Steamboat Montana at Stoner's Landing, Flathead Lake, undated; 74-232
    - Steamboat New Klondike at Safety Island, Flathead Lake, Montana, undated; 74-233
    - Steamboat Montana at Big Arm, Montana on Flathead Lake, undated; 74-234
    - New Klondike, Kalispell, and City of Polson at dock in Somers, Montana, undated; 74-235
    - Steamboat New Klondike on Flathead Lake, Montana, undated; 74-236
    - Steamboat Maryett on Flathead Lake, Montana, undated; 74-237
    - Steamers New Klondike and Montana at Somers, Montana on Flathead Lake, 1910; 74-238
    - Steamboat Montana on Flathead Lake, Montana, circa 1915; 74-239
    - Steamboat New Klondike on Flathead Lake, Montana, undated; 74-240
    - Moving a railroad steam engine on a barge on Flathead Lake, Montana, undated; 74-241
    - Steamboat Wasco and barge arriving at Polson, Montana, 1908; 74-242
    - Steamboat Silver City on Flathead Lake, Montana, undated; 74-243
    - Steamboats Mary Ann and State Of Montana at Demersville, 1891; 74-244
    - Steamboat New Klondike at Polson, Montana dock on Flathead, undated; 74-245
    - Tug Boat Paul Bunyan on Flathead Lake, Montana, undated; 74-246
    - Steamboat Helena on Flathead Lake, Montana, undated; 74-247
    - Steamboat New Klondike on Flathead Lake, Montana, undated; 74-248
    - Steamboats Montana and Flyer at Somers, Montana, dock, undated; 74-249
    - Steamboat Kalispell on Flathead Lake, Montana, undated; 74-250
    - Lisma's Ferry loaded with sheep, 1907; 81-48
    - Unidentified steamship Indian man standing near teepee in winter camp near Flathead Lake., circa 1902; 82-226
    - Unidentified steamship, probably New Klondike on Flathead Lake, undated; 82-228
    - Herridult's Ferry on Flathead River just before Flathead Lake, being pushed by boats to Papoose Island, Flathead Lake, circa 1955; 82-231
    - Steamship Montana- formerly the Wasco, built at Rollins-on Flathead Lake., undated; 82-232
    - B-10 Martin at city airport, Kalispell, circa 1936; 82-239
    - B-10 Martin at city airport, Kalispell, circa 1936; 82-240
    - B-10 Martin at city airport, Kalispell, circa 1936; 82-241
    - B-10 Martin at city airport, Kalispell. Lone Pine State Park (present) is in the background, circa 1936; 82-242
    - Steamship Klondyke, docked with passengers on deck, circa 1909; 82-243
    - Tug Paul Bunyan under construction at Somers Lumber Yard. Men left to right are: Gabriel Peterson, Fred West, Hagbord Hansen, Nils Borch, circa 1926; 82-244
    - Construction of tug Howard James at Somers Lumber Yard. Built by J. W. Swanson (man in the middle) rebuilt several times till it was replaced by the Paul Bunyan, circa 1913; 82-245
    - Ethel on Lake McDonald - built by J.W. Swanson in 1911-named after the niece of Frank Kelley-72 ft. long gas launch, undated; 83-41
    - Ethel and Lewtana on Lake McDonald. First boat is the Ethel. Second boat is the Lewtana built by J. W. Swanson, formerly the City of Polson when it ran on Flathead Lake. Moved to Lake McDonald via Flathead River, circa 1913-1914; 83-42
    - Steamship Marion at Haleyon, B.C., undated; 83-44
    - Lewtana at dock, Lake McDonald, 1920s; 83-45
    - Lewtana at dock, Lake McDonald, 1920s; 83-46
    - St. Mary's boat on Upper St. Mary's Lake; looking west just west of Narrows, 1920; 83-47
    - Cassie D on Lake McDonald. Built by Peterson of Kalispell about 1912 and ran on Flathead Lake-then owned by O'Denney-moved to Lake McDonald in 1914-gas launch 54 ft. By 9.5 ft., circa 1914; 83-48
    - Cassie D on Lake McDonald. Built by Peterson of Kalispell about 1912 and ran on Flathead Lake-then owned by O'Denney-moved to Lake McDonald in 1914-gas launch 54 ft. By 9.5 ft., circa 1914; 83-49
    - KEE-O-MEE on Flathead Lake. Built by J.W. Swanson for Bert Saling and Clifford Sherman. Burned in the early 1930s. Gas launch, named by Harry Stanford-means "a long way" in some Indian language, circa 1920-1930; 83-75
  - Soldiers, Indians, and Cowboys, 1877-1911; Subseries 3; 0.6 linear feet; 142 photos
    This subseries contains photos relating to White's research and writing on the interaction of people in the American west.
    - Indian man, possibly White Calf, putting a snake into his mouth, 1898; 137(VIII):393
    - Joseph's encampment, circa 1903; 137(VIII):394
    - "Bloods: The Horn Society of Alberta Indians", circa 1906; 137(VIII):395
    - Chief Joe Healy and Braves from Alberta, circa 1906; 137(VIII):396
    - Old time Piegan woman with travois and papoose in Alberta, circa 1906; 137(VIII):397
    - Two Indian women pictured in front of teepee. Photo by J. Fahey, undated; 137(VIII):398
    - Large group of Indians pictured, circa 1909; 137(VIII):399
    - Young Flathead Indian near Arlee, Montana, circa 1906; 137(VIII):400
    - Piegan Dancers near Browning, Montana, circa 1898; 137(VIII):401
    - Small framed Chief Aeneas, circa 1890; 137(VIII):402
    - Small group of Indians pictured including P. Pichette, John Vandenburg, Louis Nine-Pipe, and Ineas Grango. Photo by Carling Malouf, undated; 137(VIII):403
    - Unidentified man in a headdress, undated; 137(VIII):404
    - Mixed group of unidentified cowboys and Indians, circa 1890; 137(VIII):405
    - An Indian family, possibly Thomas Stabs By Mistake and his wife and son. Photo by Jane Conway, circa 1915; 137(VIII):406
    - Group of tepees near St. Mary's Lake in Glacier Park. Photo by Jane Conway, circa 1915; 137(VIII):407
    - Group of tepees near St. Mary's Lake in Glacier Park. Photo by Jane Conway, circa 1915; 137(VIII):408
    - Thomas Stabs By Mistake shooting a bow. Photo by Jane Conway, circa 1915; 137(VIII):409
    - Group of five Indians sitting on the grass. Photo by Jane Conway, circa 1915; 137(VIII):410
    - Group of five Indians riding horses. Photo by Jane Conway, circa 1915; 137(VIII):411
    - Indians near Cracker Lake. Photo by Jane Conway, circa 1915; 137(VIII):412
    - Indians near Ptarmigan Lake. Photo by Jane Conway, circa 1915; 137(VIII):413
    - Two unidentified Indians. Photo by Jane Conway, circa 1915; 137(VIII):414
    - Indians near Glacier Lake. Photo by Jane Conway, circa 1915; 137(VIII):415
    - Indians near Glacier Park. Photo by Jane Conway, circa 1915; 137(VIII):416
    - Indians near Glacier Park. Photo by Jane Conway, circa 1915; 137(VIII):417
    - Indians near Glacier Park. Photo by Jane Conway around Lake Berg., circa 1915; 137(VIII):418
    - Group of Indians getting ready for a medicine ceremony near Upper St. Mary's Lake. Photo by Jane Conway, circa 1915; 137(VIII):419; Previously assigned photo number 82-227
    - Pack horse carrying lumber through Glacier Park. Photo by Jane Conway, circa 1915; 137(VIII):420
    - Pack horse carrying lumber through Glacier Park. Photo by Jane Conway, circa 1915; 137(VIII):421
    - Two unidentified Indians; possibly man and wife?, undated; 137(VIII):422
    - Two unidentified Indians in front of tepee with a wagon, undated; 137(VIII):423
    - Small group of Indians in an urban setting, undated; 137(VIII):424
    - An elderly woman smoking a pipe and with a cane, undated; 137(VIII):425
    - Group unidentified male Indians, undated; 137(VIII):426
    - Male Indian playing a drum, undated; 137(VIII):427
    - White woman and female Indian in front of a large tepee, undated; 137(VIII):428
    - Male Indian with tomahawk, undated; 137(VIII):429
    - Large group of encamped Indians, undated; 137(VIII):430
    - Male Indian in full headdress, undated; 137(VIII):431
    - Two unidentified Indians, undated; 137(VIII):432
    - Three unidentified Indians; two older men, one child, undated; 137(VIII):433
    - Unidentified Indians dancing in some type of ceremony, undated; 137(VIII):434
    - Group four unidentified Indians; 2 male, 2 female, undated; 137(VIII):435
    - Two horses, one with a small child in a papoose and an older woman standing next to them, undated; 137(VIII):436
    - Several unidentified Indians on horseback, undated; 137(VIII):437
    - Single white horse, possibly Indian Palace Car, undated; 137(VIII):438
    - Unidentified Indians dancing in some type of ceremony, undated; 137(VIII):439
    - Two unidentified Indians in front of some incomplete structure, possibly earth lodge, undated; 137(VIII):440
    - Large group of unidentified Indians, undated; 137(VIII):441
    - A large encampment of tepees pictured from afar, undated; 137(VIII):443
    - Pile of old junk including a skull, chair, chest of drawers and shelves, undated; 137(VIII):444
    - An unidentified male Indian, undated; 137(VIII):445
    - Group seven unidentified male Indians, undated; 137(VIII):446
    - White woman along with a family of unidentified Indians, undated; 137(VIII):447
    - Unidentified Indian man and his son, undated; 137(VIII):448
    - Unidentified Indian man, undated; 137(VIII):449
    - Group a large group of Indians and one white man on a horse, undated; 137(VIII):450
    - Two unidentified elderly Indian women, undated; 137(VIII):451
    - An unidentified Indian man and his young daughter in front of a horse, undated; 137(VIII):452
    - Two Indian women cleaning, with tepee in background, undated; 137(VIII):453
    - Elderly Indian women with cane and pipe, undated; 137(VIII):454
    - Three unidentified Indians; 2 male, 1 female, undated; 137(VIII):455
    - Unidentified male Indian in headdress, undated; 137(VIII):456
    - Group four unidentified Indians; 2 male, 2 female, undated; 137(VIII):457
    - Lone male Indian, undated; 137(VIII):458
    - Group two unidentified female Indians with one young girl in front of tepee, undated; 137(VIII):459
    - Large group of unidentified Indians, most seated, undated; 137(VIII):460
    - Unidentified male Indian, undated; 137(VIII):461
    - An unfinished earth lodge, undated; 137(VIII):462
    - Large group of unidentified Indians, undated; 137(VIII):463
    - Unidentified female Indian carrying something on her back, undated; 137(VIII):464
    - Older unidentified male Indian in headdress, undated; 137(VIII):465
    - Two unidentified women (one with pipe) and one child, undated; 137(VIII):466
    - Group Indian children, undated; 137(VIII):467
    - Two Indian children in a field, undated; 137(VIII):468
    - Group of unidentified Indian males seated and smoking a pipe, undated; 137(VIII):469
    - A group, possibly trying raise a tepee, while one man stands on top of it, undated; 137(VIII):470
    - Indian, possibly White Calf, putting a snake into his mouth (same as #393), 1898; 137(VIII):471
    - Chief Lawyer (copy), circa 1880s; 137(VIII):472
    - John Delaware, Flathead (copy), 1877; 137(VIII):473
    - Kootenai Indian and canoe on Kootenai River in Idaho (from R.H. McKay collection), undated; 137(VIII):474
    - Left to right: Crawford, Corky Jones and unknown, photo courtesy of Everett Baker and George Sheperd, undated; 137(VIII):475
    - Photo from N.W. Mounted Police, from Baker, undated; 137(VIII):476
    - Photo from N.W. Mounted Police, from Baker, undated; 137(VIII):477
    - Indians near Flathead Lake, on left is Bill Savio, woman with cane is Kookooslotale, undated; 137(VIII):478
    - Pierre Paul, Lala See, Pacale and Antley, hanged in Missoula, from D.C. Johns collection, 1890; 137(VIII):479
    - Captain D.B. Wilson and "Buffalo Soldiers" at Demersville, copy from Johns collection, 1890; 137(VIII):480
    - Captain D.B. Wilson and "Buffalo Soldiers" at Demersville, copy from Johns collection, enlargement of 137(VIII):480, 1890; 137(VIII):481
    - "Chief Aeneas and part of band" looking NW, main street, Kalispell, from Johns collection, 1892; 137(VIII):482
    - "Cap. Wilson Lieut and Dr. Cole colored troops from Ft. Missoula soldiers and Camp Demersville" from Johns collection, 1890; 137(VIII):483
    - North side of main street showing two blocks of Demersville, 1891; 137(VIII):484
    - Left to right: Hank Norris, Martin Hawkins, Joe Kipp and an unidentified doctor, from Fred Hawkins collection, 1898; 137(VIII):485
    - Dan Knapp and his horses on the Fort Peck Indian Reservation at Oswego, photo by Ernest White, circa 1906; 137(VIII):486
    - Ernest White's horses with unidentified cowboy, 1907; 137(VIII):487
    - Man picking up cow chips for fuel, 1907; 137(VIII):488
    - Horse, probably on Fort Peck Indian Reservation, photo by Ernest White, 1907; 137(VIII):489
    - Lawina Medicine Cloud, photo courtesy of J.L. Long, undated; 137(VIII):490
    - Chief Lone Dog, photo courtesy of Mrs. Walking eagle, Poplar, Montana, undated; 137(VIII):491
    - Crow Indians branding cattle, photo courtesy of Montana Historical Society, 1890; 137(VIII):492
    - Branding cattle when 1530 head were issued to the Indians of Fort Belknap, photo courtesy of Montana Historical Society, circa 1900; 137(VIII):493
    - Indians branding cattle near the Sarcee Indian Reserve of southwest Calgary (from the Glenbow Institute, Calgary), circa 1890; 137(VIII):494
    - Harry Frank Dwelle (center) and others(from Dwelle), circa 1898-1905; 137(VIII):506
    - Elmo Co., driver Bob Vinvent, circa 1910; 137(VIII):507
    - Driver Tom Mueli at Dayton, Montana, 1910-1911; 137(VIII):508
    - Heading for Somers, 1911; 137(VIII):509
    - Harry Frank Dwelle shortly after he sold Grayling Inn, undated; 137(VIII):510
    - Flathead dancer, 1908; 137(VIII):511
    - Large group of Flathead Indians pictured, undated; 137(VIII):512
    - Medicine Lodge, undated; 137(VIII):513
    - Two Flathead Indians pictured, 1908; 137(VIII):514
    - Group the Horn Society of Flathead Indians, 1907; 137(VIII):515
    - Chief Joe Healy and Braves, 1907; 137(VIII):516
    - Group of Indians, including Chief Aeneas, 1892; 137(VIII):517
    - Indian on horseback, circa 1908; 137(VIII):518
    - Indian encampment, 1898; 137(VIII):519
    - Group Flatheads on horseback, undated; 137(VIII):520
    - Group, likely ranchers and farmers, undated; 137(VIII):521
    - Baptise Mathias (Kootenai Chief) and two other Indians pictured, undated; 137(VIII):522
    - Group Indians, including Baptise Mathias, ?1930?; 137(VIII):523
    - Stagecoach "Camas to Plains," Flathead Indian Reservation, Montana, circa 1910; 137(VIII):524
    - Piegan woman with travois and papoose with child, 1906; 137(VIII):525
    - Group Dancers of Somers, Montana, circa 1909; 137(VIII):526
    - Two unidentified Indians, undated; 137(VIII):527
    - Two male Flathead Indians, undated; 137(VIII):528
    - Group of Indians pictured at Spotted Eagle's Camp, undated; 137(VIII):529
    - Group Blackfoot Indian Braves, undated; 137(VIII):530
    - Unknown Indian wearing headdress, undated; 137(VIII):531
    - Suzette, wife of Kustata (x2), undated; 137(VIII):531a
    - Chief Aeneas (x2), undated; 137(VIII):531b
    - Chief Isaac, brother to Kustata (x2), undated; 137(VIII):531c
    - Chief Kustata (x2), 137(VIII):531d
    - Unknown man on Eastern Montana Plains, undated; 81-36
    - J.J. Barnes and family, Fred Long sheep camp on Pondera Creek, Montana, 1909; 81-42
    - Ed White on horse, 1905-1907; 81-44
    - Camp tender gathering cow chips for fuel on the Teton River, Montana, J.B. Long Co., 1905; 81-49
    - Gambler, later a herder for J.B. Long Co., 1905-1907; 81-60
    - Mike and the Kit foxes on Police Creek, Montana, 1909-1910; 81-64
    - Ed Dent and pups, 1905-1907; 81-66
    - Woman standing is Mrs. Charging Dog with husband on her left, Bad Hawk, in light clothing; Oswego, Montana; at railroad depot, 1907; 81-99
    - Dan Knopp and his saddle horses at Oswego, Montana, 1907; 81-100
    - Man and horse on Eastern Montana plains, undated; 81-105
    - Unidentified group of people, eastern MT, undated; 81-107
  - Nature and Animals, 1898-1973; Subseries 4; 0.2 linear feet; 59 photos
    This subseries contains photographs of nature scenes and various animals, mostly in Montana.
    - Dog standing on the edge of a dock, circa 1940; 137(VIII):532
    - Bridge across the Pend d'Oreille in Polson, Montana, 1920; 137(VIII):533
    - Photo at Lake and Flathead County line, 1905; 137(VIII):534
    - Men cutting ice near Polson, Montana, 1912; 137(VIII):535
    - Pend d'Oreille near Polson, Montana, circa 1937; 137(VIII):536
    - Stone masons from Butte, Montana, at Narrows of St. Mary's Lake, circa 1932; 137(VIII):537
    - Type of pond weed in Flathead Lake, undated; 137(VIII):538
    - Coyote carcass twisted up in fence, "Death on Fence", 1959; 137(VIII):539
    - Narrows of St. Mary's Lake (upper), two men pictured in the distance, circa 1898; 137(VIII):540
    - Typical buffalo country on the Frenchman River, Canada, 1960; 137(VIII):541
    - Looking up North Fork Big Hole toward Trail Creek, 1962; 137(VIII):542
    - Looking east up the Selway River, Idaho, undated; 137(VIII):543
    - Looking 20 degrees South, exploration of Nez Perce Trail, 1975; 137(VIII):544
    - "Crossing the Lake-Kootenai," (Historical Society of Montana), circa 1909; 137(VIII):545
    - "Crossing the Pend d'Oreille-Kalispell", undated; 137(VIII):546
    - "Country of the Kootenai", undated; 137(VIII):547
    - Medicine Rock Pass, 1968; 137(VIII):548
    - Lithograph "Flathead Lake Looking Southward", 1968; 137(VIII):549
    - View of Flathead Lake, 1968; 137(VIII):550
    - Looking southward, Flathead Lake west shore, 1968; 137(VIII):551
    - Flathead Lake, showing Miller Point in distant center, 1968; 137(VIII):552
    - Douglas Island, Miller Point and Table Bay, 1968; 137(VIII):553
    - Flathead Lake, 1968; 137(VIII):554
    - Medicine Rock Pass in distance, 1968; 137(VIII):555
    - Location where Pacale reportedly covered J.M. Dunn with brush, also where the cartridge was located, 1962; 137(VIII):556
    - Man wandering around near soldier's camp, undated; 137(VIII):557
    - Dan Knapp's horses on the Fort Peck Indian Reservation, unknown herdsman, circa 1906; 137(VIII):558
    - Ernest White's horse he bought from Dan Knapp, 1907; 137(VIII):559
    - White's horses, 1907; 137(VIII):560
    - White's horses, 1907; 137(VIII):561
    - Looking toward Rosebud Creek, 1961; 137(VIII):562
    - Williams Junction, 1973; 137(VIII):563
    - Near Miles City or Billings, Montana, undated; 137(VIII):564
    - Near Helena, heading for White Sulphur Spring (MT Historical Society), undated; 137(VIII):565
    - Tree, 1906; 137(VIII):566
    - Pleasant Valley, Idaho, 1973; 137(VIII):567
    - Pleasant Valley, Idaho, 1973; 137(VIII):568
    - Medicine Lodge Pass, 1973; 137(VIII):569
    - Gilmore, Idaho, 1973; 137(VIII):570
    - Gilmore, Idaho, 1973; 137(VIII):571
    - Point of rocks, as of 1973, 137(VIII):572
    - pusher on Gilmore and Pittsburgh L. Bannock Pass, circa 1920 (from Baker), 137(VIII):573
    - Pine Butte, north side, 1973; 137(VIII):574
    - East end of Pine Butte, 1973; 137(VIII):575
    - Polson, Montana, undated; 137(VIII):576
    - Oil rig near Kintla Lake, North Fork of the Flathead, Montana, circa 1925; 137(VIII):576a
    - J.J. Barnes, Pondera Creek, Montana, 1909; 81-34
    - View of Montana Plains, undated; 81-35
    - 7,000 lambs on trail, J.B. Long Co., 1905-1907; 81-62
    - 7,000 lambs on trail, J.B. Long Co., 1905-1907; 81-63
    - View of Milk River with Nashua in center distance, 1905-1907; 81-65
    - 3,000 "big weathers" on Basin Coulee, 1905-1907; 81-67
    - Bad land hill, 1905-1907; 81-68
    - Imported Percheron horse, 1905-1907; 81-69
    - 3,000 sheep on Nelson's Reservoir, Montana, undated; 81-87
    - Sheep being brought across river by small boat, undated; 81-106
    - Sheep on new bridge (cement floor cost $101,000) between Big Arm and Polson, 1929; 81-110
    - Sheep on new bridge (cement floor cost $101,000) between Big Arm and Polson, 1929; 81-111
    - Sheep of Flathead Lake Sheep Company headed east for hay on Polson street, 1929; 81-112
    - Oil rig in what is now Glacier Park. Perhaps the Butte or Kintla oil well near head of Kintla Lake, circa 1925; 82-248
  - European, 1914-1978; Subseries 5; 0.2 linear feet; 47 photos
    This subseries contains photos of European subjects.
    - Hellfire corner, on the Main Road, Belgium, 1917; 137(VIII):494a
    - Hellfire corner, on the Main Road, Belgium, 1917; 137(VIII):494b
    - Ruins of the cathedral at Albert France, 1916; 137(VIII):494c
    - Ruins of the cathedral at Albert France, 1978; 137(VIII):494d
    - British cavalry passing the ruined basilica of Notre Dame de Brebieres, Albert, France, October 8, 1918; 137(VIII):495
    - Notre Dame de Brebieres, Albert, France, 1978; 137(VIII):495a
    - British military band playing in the Grand Place in Arras, France, April 29, 1917; 137(VIII):495b
    - Grand Place in Arras, France, 1978; 137(VIII):495c
    - Four American Doughboys running from artillery fire, Exermont, France, 1918; 137(VIII):496
    - American troops advancing toward Sedan, Thelonne, France, October 1918; 137(VIII):497
    - Thelonne, France, 1978; 137(VIII):498
    - British cavalry passing the ruined basilica of Notre Dame de Brebieres, Albert, France, August 8, 1918; 137(VIII):499
    - Notre Dame, 1978; 137(VIII):500
    - Belgian cavalry in Farness, 1914; 137(VIII):501
    - German troops of the 18th Division, IX Corps, in the Grand Place, Mons, Belgium, August 24, 1914; 137(VIII):502
    - Casualties outside a church, Peruyse, Belgium, November 1, 1914; 137(VIII):503
    - British troops at Ypres, Belgium, October 13, 1914; 137(VIII):504
    - Battle of Menin Road Ridge, German prisoners being marched through the Cathedral Square, Ypres, Belgium, September 20, 1917; 137(VIII):505
    - Exermont, France, 1978; 137(VIII):577
    - Bailleul, France, 1918; 137(VIII):578
    - Bailleul, France, 1978; 137(VIII):579
    - Furness, Belgium, 1978; 137(VIII):580
    - King George, King Albert, Prince of Wales and Queen Mary, Furness, Belgium, 1914; 137(VIII):581
    - Furness, Belgium, 1978; 137(VIII):582
    - King George, King Albert and the Prince of Wales, Furness, Belgium, 1978; 137(VIII):583
    - Furness, Belgium, 1978; 137(VIII):584
    - Mons, Belgium, 1978; 137(VIII):585
    - Peruyse, Belgium, 1978; 137(VIII):586
    - Zillebeke Road, Ypres, Belgium, October 15, 1914; 137(VIII):587
    - Zillebeke Road, Ypres, Belgium, 1978; 137(VIII):588
    - Capture of Cambrai, France, October 9, 1918; 137(VIII):589
    - Cambrai, France, 1978; 137(VIII):590
    - United Art Volunteer Rifles, marching in London, March 1915; 137(VIII):591
    - London, 1978; 137(VIII):592
    - British Royal Naval machine gun cars in the square at Furnes, Belgium, 1914; 137(VIII):593
    - Furnes, Belgium, 1978; 137(VIII):594
    - Lous, France, September 28, 1915; 137(VIII):595
    - Lous, France, 1978; 137(VIII):596
    - "Death in the Afternoon," after fighting in Cambrai, France, circa 1917-1918; 137(VIII):597
    - Ruins in the square at Cambrai, France, October 23, 1918; 137(VIII):598
    - Cambrai, France, 1978; 137(VIII):599
    - Ypres, Belgium, 1978; 137(VIII):600